knowyourmoney.co.uk 2018-01-31

# Privacy and Cookies Policy | Know Your Money

As a Know Your Money user we take your privacy very seriously. Under the Data Protection Act 1998 we have an obligation to ensure that all the information held and processed about you complies with the principles of the Act. You are entitled to know how we intend to use any information you provide, to then decide if you want to give it to us.

Therefore, for your peace of mind, we have outlined our practices regarding data protection below.

Notice Media Ltd is the data controller, registered with the Information Commissioners Office for the Data Protection Act under Z955517X

## The information we hold about you & what we use it for: 

If you choose to sign up to one of our email services, we will only hold your name and email address. 

We do not pass on any of your personal information to third parties without your given consent. 

The facility to unsubscribe is available within the emails. 

If you choose to be contacted by a third party via one of our product contact request forms, we will capture your name, postcode, email & contact number. In addition, you may also provide further details relating to the specific product you wish to be contacted about. This will only be used for the purpose specified and to fulfil your request. 

If you click through to one of the many third parties within our comparison tables or advertising, any information you provide to them will be held by them in accordance with their own policies and applicable legislation, and you will need to contact them directly. 

In addition, we will also hold anonymised information about your computer and about your visits to the Know Your Money website which may include information about your IP address, geographical location, browser type, length of visit and which pages you viewed to help improve the user experience on the website.

## How to view, change or remove the data we hold about you:

Under the Data Protection Act you have the right to access information we hold about you. If you would like to request the information we hold about you, delete or change it, or opt-out of emails, product contact request forms, email us on **advertising@noticemedia.co.uk** or write to us at:

**Notice Media Ltd  
Floor 3 Haldin House  
Old Bank of England Court  
Queen Street  
Norwich  
Norfolk  
NR2 4SX**

## Cookies- What is a cookie?

'Cookies' are small text files that are stored by the browser on your computer or mobile phone. Websites are able to read and write these files, allowing them store things like personalisation details or user preferences. 

Know Your Money uses 'cookies' to ascertain how people navigate and use the website. This information is subsequently used to make the website more user-friendly. The information stored in the 'cookie' is not linked in anyway to any personal information that we hold in our database.

A visit to a page on KnowYourMoney.co.uk may generate the following cookie:

Name: 'Paid User Cookie'

Description: This is used to identify which publisher, website and advertisement a click or transaction originated from. The information tracked within this cookie is anonymous and cannot be tied to any personally identifiable information.

## 3rd Party cookies on Know Your Money

Google Analytics:

We use Google Analytics to measure the behavior of users on the website, this statistical information is stored on the users computer using a cookie so we can evaluate your use of the KnowYourMoney website. For more information or to opt out of this the Google privacy policy is listed below:

<http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacypolicy.html>

Crazyegg:

We use crazyegg to evaluate how visitors are interacting with our web pages so we can improve the customer journey. Crazy Egg does not collect information about visitor behaviour over multiple sites and does not aggregate information from any other sources about browsing patterns of individual visitors across multiple sites. The cookie information does not include personal data such as name, age, phone number, e-mail address or mailing address nor does Crazy Egg link cookies to personal data such as name, age, phone number, e-mail address or mailing address.

<http://www.crazyegg.com/privacy>

## Advertising:

The advertisements that you see displayed on our website are delivered on our behalf by Google. No information which identifies you, for example your name, address, email address or telephone number, is used to provide this advertising. In order to display advertising most likely to be relevant to you Google may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. This cookie does not collect personal data about you nor is it linked to any identifiable information about you. These third party advertising cookies may be used by those third parties to anonymously target advertising to you on other websites, based on your visit to KnowYourMoney.co.uk. Because of how cookies work, KnowYourMoney.co.uk cannot access these cookies, nor can the third parties access the data in cookies used by KnowYourMoney.co.uk

You can find out more information and opt out of Googles use of cookies by the page below:

<http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/>

## How do I turn cookies off?

If you would not like for this information to be recorded in this way you can choose to disable cookies through your internet browser by following the step by step instructions below for each browser:

If you are concerned about the use of cookies generated by advertisers and how these are used you can find our more information from the consumer website created by the Internet Advertising Bureau (IAB) - www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/

Important - Use of knowyourmoney.co.uk is subject to our Terms of Use

### Important information

Knowyourmoney.co.uk is a free service with no charge to the user, for more details on how our site works click here.

Knowyourmoney.co.uk is a trading style of Notice Media Ltd, Registered Office: Floor 3 Haldin House, Old Bank of England Court, Queen Street, Norwich, Norfolk NR2 4SX Registered in England & Wales No 05409985 and also in accordance with the Data Protection Act (1988) Registration Number: Z955517X

Notice Media is authorised and regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority, FRN 771521. In respect of consumer credit, knowyourmoney.co.uk acts as a credit broker - not a lender.
